[
    {
    "question" : "'OS' computer abbreviation usually means?",
    "choice1": "Order of Significance",
    "choice2": "Open Software",
    "choice3": "Operating System",
    "choice4": "Optical Sensor",
    "answer": 3
},

{
    "question": "'.MOV' extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
    "choice1": "Image file",
    "choice2": "Animation/movie file",
    "choice3": "Audio file",
    "choice4": "MS Office document",
    "answer": 2
},
{ 
    "question": "'.MPG' extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
    "choice1": "Word Perfect Document file",
    "choice2": "MS Office document",
    "choice3": "Animation/movie file",
    "choice4": "Image file",
    "answer": 3
},
{    
    "question": "Who developed Yahoo?",
    "choice1": "Dennis Ritchie & Ken Thompson",
    "choice2": "David Filo & Jerry Yang",
    "choice3": "Vint Cerf & Robert Kahn",
    "choice4": "Steve Case & Jeff Bezos",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    
    "question": "'DB' computer abbreviation usually means?",
    "choice1": "Database",
    "choice2": "Double Byte",
    "choice3": "Data Block",
    "choice4": "Driver Boot",
    "answer": 1
},
{
    
    "question": "'.INI' extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
    "choice1": "Image file",
    "choice2": "System file",
    "choice3": "Hypertext related file",
    "choice4": "Image Color Matching Profile file",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    
    "question": "The sampling rate, (how many samples per second are stored) for a CD is?",
    "choice1": "48.4 kHz",
    "choice2": "22,050 Hz",
    "choice3": "44.1 kHz",
    "choice4": "48 kHz",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "What do we call a network whose elements may be separated by some distance? It usually involves two or more small networks and dedicated high-speed telephone lines.",
    "choice1": "URL (Universal Resource Locator)",
    "choice2": "LAN (Local Area Network)",
    "choice3": "WAN (Wide Area Network)",
    "choice4": "World Wide Web",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "Sometimes computers and cache registers in a foodmart are connected to a UPS system. What does UPS mean?",
    "choice1": "United Parcel Service",
    "choice2": "Uniform Product Support",
    "choice3": "Under Paneling Storage",
    "choice4": "Uninterruptable Power Supply",
    "answer": 4
},
{
    "question": "What is FMD?",
    "choice1": "Fast-Ethernet Measuring Device",
    "choice2": "Flashing Media Diode",
    "choice3": "Fluorescent Multi-Layer Disc",
    "choice4": "Flash Media Driver",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "What is a URL?",
    "choice1": "A computer software program",
    "choice2": "A type of UFO",
    "choice3": "The address of a document or 'page' on the World Wide Web",
    "choice4": "An acronym for Uniform Resources Learning",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "What does SSL stand for?",
    "choice1": "Secure Socket Layer",
    "choice2": "System Socket Layer",
    "choice3": "Superuser System Login",
    "choice4": "Secure System Login",
    "answer": 3
},
{
    "question": "Which of these is a documented hoax virus?",
    "choice1": "McDonalds screensaver",
    "choice2": "Alien.worm",
    "choice3": "Merry Xmas",
    "choice4": "Adolph",
    "answer": 1
},
{
    "question": "What is part of a database that holds only one type of information?",
    "choice1": "Report",
    "choice2": "Field",
    "choice3": "Record",
    "choice4": "File",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    "question": "The Central Processing Unit is an embedded chip that acts as the 'brains' of a computer. What Intel chip was used in the Altair (the first real personal computer)?",
    "choice1": "6502",
    "choice2": "8080",
    "choice3": "6400",
    "choice4": "8286",
    "answer": 2
},
{
    "question": "'.TMP' extension refers usually to what kind of file?",
    "choice1": "Compressed Archive file",
    "choice2": "Image file",
    "choice3": "Temporary file",
    "choice4": "Audio file",
    "answer": 3
}
]